Live forever or die trying.
In Time is a action, thriller, science fiction film directed by Andrew Niccol.
In the not-too-distant future, the aging gene has been switched off.
To avoid overpopulation, time has become the currency and the
way people pay for luxuries and necessities.
The rich can live forever, while the rest struggle
to negotiate for their immortality.
A poor young man who suddenly comes into a fortune of time finds himself on the
run from a corrupt police force known as the "time keepers".
Will Salas, played by Justin Timberlake.
Sylvia Weis, played by Amanda Seyfried.
Raymond Leon, played by Cillian Murphy.
Rachel Salas, played by Olivia Wilde.
Fortis, played by Alex Pettyfer.
Borel, played by Johnny Galecki.
In Time is a 2011 American science fiction action film
written, co-produced, and directed by Andrew Niccol.
Justin Timberlake and Amanda Seyfried star as inhabitants of a society that uses time from one's lifespan as its primary
currency, with each individual possessing a clock on their arm that counts down how long they have to live.
Cillian Murphy, Vincent Kartheiser, Olivia Wilde, Matt Bomer,
Johnny Galecki, and Alex Pettyfer also star.
The film was released on October 28, 2011, and grossed
$174 million against a $40 million budget.
It received mixed reviews from critics, who praised the
premise while criticizing its execution.
The film explores themes of future, race against
time, immortality, bank, dystopia.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.